hey everyone thanks for listening to The
Grow Your Life podcast my name is
Jeremiah Krakowski and on this podcast I
help mentors thought leaders coaches and
authors scale their businesses to
millions of dollars online and if you
don't want to make millions we can at
least get you to multiple six figures
because that's a stair step along the
way to get to Millions this is where we
break down what's working right now to
help you make sales we help you go from
zero to making the kind of income that
you want to make how to develop your
offers get more leads and then close
more sales and that's our three-part
system that we work with you through
right now now in in honor of this week
everybody is buzzing all over the
Internet about Alex hormozzi's 100
million dollar leads book launch and
I've been one of the early
um
fans of Alex hermosi telling pretty much
everybody if you've been listening to
this podcast or you follow my content
I've been telling people to to grab his
books uh his book 100 million dollar
offers this is Alex right here uh 100
million dollar offers is actually one of
my favorite books that I've been telling
people for the last pretty much since it
was released and written yeah two years
been telling people to buy this book
read it
that it's absolutely important and fits
into one of the biggest reasons why is
because
the greatest takeaway from this that I
gotta sell things that are to a group of
people that have money to spend don't
try to Market stuff to people
who don't have money to spend
don't have cash flow because otherwise
you're just trying to convince people
that they should buy from you when in
fact if you just create stuff that
people actually want you'll have a
successful business and then his his
brand new book that just came out called
100 million dollar leads I actually read
this uh in one night I you know I bought
it right here I'm a verified purchaser
of this and it's it's funny the way I
can describe this is literally if
somebody broke apart all the systems
that I have in my brain about getting
leads and running ad campaigns and
getting people on your email list it
would literally be this book and I was
talking to my mom about that is that
most of Alex's content is like it's the
closest to what we've always done it's
the closest to even what I teach and and
and it's it's really cool seeing that
you know I made a post about that on one
of his videos and somebody's like oh so
you just copy Alex's stuff and knock it
off and sell it to people I was like no
like it's not that it's that I've just
I've been doing this business for over
two decades and we've done stuff at the
same time that we both discovered
basically the same way of producing
results and so our methodology is this
it always follows this kind of same
format it's a little it's a little dull
here on this backdrop here but you want
to have a free offer that gets people on
your email list
and then you want to convert those
people to sales at I like a two-tier
where you got a thousand to two thousand
dollars and then above that you got like
six thousand to ten thousand and that's
how we're able to convert profits of
over a million dollars very easily a two
thousand dollar product you only need
500 people
in one year buying a two thousand dollar
product that's it and you could break
that down into 12 monthly payments as
well a ten thousand dollar product you
know how many you need for a million on
that you only need a hundred people at
10 grand you only need 100 people to pay
you
really uh 83 you only need 83 people to
pay you a thousand dollars a month to
make a million bucks
that's it
very simple
I think that we over complicate that
part of the process way too much okay
and so I want you to shift your mindset
in this and this is why today's is all
about converting those leads to sales
I'm not going to coddle a lot of the
mindsets
if you're at this point you've worked
through a lot of the mindset stuff and
if you're listening to this and you
haven't worked through the mindset stuff
that's fine you're just gonna have to do
a lot of this stuff scared and and sort
of go Kicking and Screaming into making
a ton of money because that's what I'm
about to tell you right now is what's
going to make you the most amount of
money in your business and so converting
leads to sales is a process of doing
really one thing really really well
and that
one thing
is building
Trust
with people
and so what we utilize to build trust
with people is we will do
a free offer doesn't cost anything
and
then we'll send them to sign up for
another free offer right here which
qualifies them so this is our low
commitment free offer
this is our high commitment free offer
and generally this is like a one day 90
minute webinar this is a five-day
or a three-day uh challenge we might
Host this once a month or once a quarter
and then we might host like four or five
of these webinars to tell those people
to sign up for the higher commitment
level so that ends up qualifying people
to where all that we're advertising and
marketing for is to get people at this
lower level and then what we do is we
utilize this higher commitment level to
actually sell people on what we're
charging money for
and we've found that that actually
qualifies people better with our paid
advertising
it'll actually cost us three to five
times as much in paid ads to go straight
to the high commitment offer and so if
we can actually we can leverage our
margins better and make more profits by
going free to free and then to paid
and we've been doing that for the last
year year and a half that's what's
growing our business to make seven
figures is going this we do like a very
simple low commitment free offer that
goes to a paid five day or a free five
day we also have a paid upsell
right here
and we do an upsell on both of these
this one the low commitment even has a
seven dollar upsell the high commitment
one has a 27 upsell
and in the upsell people get to ask
questions they get limited time bonuses
and they get the recordings of the
sessions from those so these are really
all our marketing process to do one
thing to build trust with people people
that we don't know we run an ad to
people that we've never met before to
join us for these low commitment
webinars and then we build trust with
them and listen not everybody takes
action but about 20 percent of these
people will make a commitment to go to
this level right here
and that's awesome and and and so that's
the reason why we're qualifying anybody
who's at this level
is way more qualified than somebody who
just came in through an ad over here if
I sold my program I could sell a few
programs to these people but I can sell
three to five times as much by having
them take another free commitment level
with me and so that's really cool as far
as getting our cost of our leads down
but that doesn't really tell you how to
get any sales right and so what we
utilize is we utilize virtual events
where we use video
for multiple days in a row where we're
connecting with people
and we create this sort of atmosphere
where we're solving a real problem for
people we just actually did a five-day
intensive and you can you can sort of
see it over at my website right here we
just did one of these
uh this past week the doors to our
accelerator are are the enrollment of my
paid program is open
until Tuesday August 22nd then it closes
again
um but what we did was we did a five-day
intensive
called
create and launch your profitable group
mentorship offer
and so this is where for five days I
broke down pretty much the game
of everything that you need to know and
gave away my best content for free
I gave away my best methodology for free
of how we actually create offers that
are irresistible how we write our sales
copy how do we attract leads through
paid advertising and then what's the
process of actually closing those people
as sales and that's what I'm going to
break down for you right here is that
last part of it how do you close people
to make those sales and it's all about
building trust in four things
you
your product
your brand reputation
and your track record or transformation
that you can bring to other people the
result the promised result that you're
bringing people okay so it's it's a
four-part
trust based
system let's actually write this on the
on the Whiteboard here
you want to build trust in you
that's you as the business owner like
this is like the actual person of you
you want people to feel good about
working with you and this has nothing to
do with people pleasing this has nothing
to do with
managing other people's emotions you
will piss people off you will have
haters you will have negativity that
comes at you but you're gonna also be
very irresistible and there's a group of
people that are gonna absolutely love
you and you want to build trust with
those people that you will deliver that
your word is bond and so you want them
to believe that your word is bond right
here level 10 trust in your word why is
that because now everything you say to
those people after that moment in time
they trust it they follow along you
don't need to convince them that what
you're saying is true
so I never worry about convincing anyone
of what I say is true because I'm I've
already gotten them to a level 10 of
trust with me
I've gotten them to a level 10 trust in
my
my brand
or my business or the fact that I'm
going to be there to support them my
track record I've gotten them to a level
10 trust in the result that I'm going to
be delivering to them in their business
and I've gotten them a level 10 trust in
my program
this is my mentorship program and so
when they're all at level 10 10
in all four of these quadrants right
here
the chances of them buying like buying
from you are
99.9 percent
the chances of them like even if they
don't have the money
and that's the crazy part even if they
have to scrounge the money when you can
build the trust in you
your brand your business your reputation
your company the result that you're
actually promising and your actual
program itself the support system the
accountability what they're going to get
it's money in the bank
and so my entire mission
for why I actually do the five-day event
is
it's a five-day trust building exercise
I'm taking five days
to build trust in all four of these
quadrants
with people and then I'm telling them
about my program that cost two thousand
dollars per year to register with me and
I'm not trying to convince them that
they should work with me I'm simply
giving my best value my best content of
what they can do to get started with my
program and then when I'm asking them to
pay for is the overall result and
implementation right
because they're not gonna get to this
result in five days with me
they'll begin the process
but the result comes only when they
actually register for the program itself
and so when they actually even
understand that system and how it works
and why the program is important for
them to join and that they can't just
sit on what they learned for five days
but they actually have to either join
the program or decide that it's not for
them to do this type of a thing so we
can we take them right to the the
breaking point of
if you want the result you got to pay
that's it
and and so we're sort of if you think
about it
in some sense you want them to to feel
like
it's well kind of
that their success is contingent on them
paying
for that success to come to them
it's almost like
their future
is waiting for them to pay you money and
the only way that they're going to
actually reach that future goal to see
that version of their life that they
want is if they buy from you and nobody
else and you want them to believe that
you want to get people when they're at
this level 10 trust too the other side
of it is that their belief in other
people's offers sometimes decreases a
little bit because they're weighing you
against other people as a coach and as a
mentor and it's not that you directly
attack other people I never directly
attack other people you're just so much
more above and beyond as far as what you
are promising and that's the part that's
so important if we have to be willing to
make
bold
promises
big promises to people
big promises that terrify us because we
aren't even sure if we can deliver on
them
but that is what's going to close you
sales
is when you can make those promises and
you say I'm gonna figure it out and I'm
gonna make it happen and then you put
your reputation on the line to make
those things happen
and you actually challenge yourself to
step up and do those things and you
challenge yourself to raise the bar
above yourself above what you're even
capable of
and then you actually promise that to
people if you buy this from me you will
get this
I am frequently asked by people Jeremiah
I had a bunch of people this week with
all due respect
do you actually deliver on what you say
you will because
a lot of people claim they do do you
actually do it
and what makes you different from
everybody else who claims they do but
doesn't
and and so that's how I know I hit a
bold enough promise is to where they're
actually skeptical and so that's where
the final stage of the sales process is
is to where you have people asking you
questions about the legitimacy of your
offer
I used to actually shudder when people
would do that and I learned a technique
that that actually means that they are
the most qualified buyer that if they're
asking those final questions they are
qualified and what you want to do is you
want to deliver with Excellence to those
people with without
wavering without a hitch like yes
absolutely we can make that happen for
you this is exactly how it goes agree
with everything that they want
everything that they desire and then
create a way to make that happen the
cool part is
when you get really good at this
your bold promise is your regular
version of working with you for me my
but what used to be a bold promise for
me me is just now the normal way of how
I work with people and we have rave
reviews clients that are making a ton of
money people that were skeptical about
working with us in the beginning that
now have faith and confidence in the
process that they're actually buying
into that they're excited
to start working with us and and and and
and that right there is the point where
they they go on over to our website
over at jeremycorkowski.com and they
they click on our group coaching right
here
[Laughter]
you know the doors are are open to this
right now and you know we have three
bonuses that we offer we're actually
giving away three of our courses
to people who
just sign up and just try our program
for 30 days we have a 30-day risk-free
money back guarantee so if you can take
the risk away from people
and you make it easy to pay you
see we offer a payment plan a 12 pay
option
I think anybody who wants to work with
me can find 166 dollars and 42 cents a
month and that is not expensive at all
in fact I think it's too cheap
and that's why this is the last time
we're ever offering this price to
anybody
period because that is way too cheap
whatsoever
to charge for this level of interaction
that we give you to where we work with
you where we come alongside you support
you to build your your sales copy your
sales funnel your all your offers we
help you with your your webinar content
your lead magnets
you're advertising you name it we're in
there working with you every single day
to help you have success in the great
the kind of money that you want to make
in your business
and so what we do is
in our presentation
during the five-day intensive
on the on the on the last day
which people assume we're gonna pitch
them on the last day part of our process
is we don't actually make the last two
days pitch days at all we actually give
our best value on those last days that's
where we announced the the free
giveaways that we're going to do if we
have any of those and we continue to
actually blow the lid off with value but
we end up seeding what our paid program
is so where we really sell our program
is in the follow-up emails that people
get in the actual five-day intensive we
deliver the highest level of content
during those last couple of days where
we walk people through the process and
the Cadence and the formula of what do
you say each day to to get people to buy
from you and people are blown away by by
this whole process
and then what we do is we can we send
two emails a day to anybody who signed
up for that until we close the doors and
we have a limited enrollment period for
the reason of the fact that that urgency
of the fact that they only have a short
amount of time to register and then they
can't ever again unless we decide to
open it again another time
that urgency encourages people to take
action
to not wait because we don't know if
we're going to even ever open the doors
again to our program
and so when you do that and you create
that urgency and you make it a limited
time offer you set a deadline on it and
you promise a bold promise
this will help you get more sales in
your business and the more authentic you
are at connecting with people being able
to connect through video like this
without wavering without like being
worried what people think about you
learning to flow like I am right now
where I'm just I'm just flowing I I
don't have any of this scripted none of
this is scripted this is me just talking
right now into the camera to you this
whole thing was not scripted in any way
whatsoever but I just I knew up here
what I was going to share with you the
basic idea and I just pressed record
that's and that's how we make a lot of
our content as well
now I get it if maybe you're a planner
or you're somebody that has to put all
the pieces together and have them all
perfect before you get started but I
want to encourage you in this
perfectionism is one of the greatest
things that can stop you from succeeding
and if we're worried what other people
think about us if we're worried about
looking perfect sounding perfect not
offending people not disappointing
people and that gets caught up in our
brain to where we're so worried about
doing right by everybody which I'm not
saying that you want to do wrong by
people but if you grew up like I did
there's an inordinate focus on making
sure that everything is in the right
order and it will actually harm you more
than help you because of that okay and
so when you can learn to let loose be
your authentic self
show up to where it's fun for you you're
just having fun I'm just having a
conversation with my friends that's all
I'm doing right now I'm recording this
for my friends I'm recording this for
people that have connected with me
and when you can do that and you do that
consistently you can close a ton of
sales in your business
and so listen if you if you've never
joined me for any of our Live Events
make sure to do so you'll see ads coming
across your feed for when we host them
um if you've not joined us in our client
growth accelerator I'd highly recommend
that you join us when there's enrollment
open
or get on the waiting list for the next
time that we decide to open the doors to
our accelerator program which we don't
know when that's going to be
and that's part of our process so we
don't have it open all the time
and all we end up directing people to is
free offers getting them to join us for
free to build trust in those four areas
and and and the process of building
trust really comes by demonstrating the
truth with Integrity about those four
areas handling objections learning to
have confidence learning to show up with
confidence even if you don't know if
it's going to produce results for me I
had to learn how to show up with
confidence and I didn't believe in
myself when I first started and I didn't
think that I was worth people listening
to and I learned to develop The
Confidence from within that even though
I didn't fully believe in myself I could
still show up as my strongest most
powerful self when I gave a presentation
one way that I did this is I would watch
other people get presentations I would
Channel their energy I would say okay
let me see their energy how are they
being let me model that let me sort of
imitate it but in my own way and that's
how I've developed my own Cadence for
for speaking is looking at how other
speakers speak their Cadence of how they
talk how they communicate and then
creating sort of my own take on that
that has evolved over the years okay
and so it's not rocket science my
friends to be able to make twenty to
forty thousand dollars a month in your
own mentorship business
start believing that that's possible for
you this year the next 12 months if
you're in our accelerator program we'll
walk you through how to do that
thanks for being here I'm excited to
work with you in the future share this
episode with somebody and we'll talk
soon grow your life have a good one
[Music]
[Applause]
foreign